KOUSSOUR YOUNES

Full Stack Web Developer .NET

- ➤ Younesksr99@gmail.com
- +212 699965272
- 20570 CASABLANCA, Morocco
- in Younes KOUSSOUR

SKILLS

- Punctual
- Team Work
- Responsability
- Dynamic
- Curious

S LANGUAGES		
Arabe		
English		
French		

↔ HOBBIES

Travel, Soccer, Swimming, Music

d organizations

CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

ASSOCIATION AMBITION JEUNES 2022 – present

PROFILE

Am KOUSSOURE Younes .NET developer. Qualified professional with approximately two year of experience in project development, in particular, the design of websites and applications autonomous on my position while enjoying teamwork. My early experiences sufficiently developed teamwork.

I am looking to take up new challenges to boost my career.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering, *ALX MOROCCO* 2023 – present | Casablanca, MOROCCO

Formation : SKILLS FOR SUCCESS, *ENCG* 2020 – 2021 | CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

Technician Specialized in Computer Science, *ISGI* 2018 – 2020 | CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

Baccalaureate Option Life Sciences And Earth, High school ABDELKRIM KHATTABI 2017 – 2018 | CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Analyst Developer .NET, FINREG GROUP 2022 – present | CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

- Analyze client's needs.
- Databases Management.
- Creation of WEB apps using MVC & N-Tier Architecture.
- Development of WEB & Mobile applications.
- Creation and deployment of REST API.

Maintenance, bug fixes and improvements

EQUIPIER, *McDonald's* 2019 – 2019 | CASABLANCA, MOROCCO

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS	
PROFESSIONAL SKILLS	
SQL	
ASP.NET	
Front-end & Back-end	



MS Office Microsoft/2019 (77-882:Excel)